Where O
is O
Berlin B-LOC
? O

I O
like O
Shaka B-PERSON
Khan I-PERSON

24MAR2022 B-DATE
testing O

888-183280-123 B-ACCNUM
accont O
number O

00700 B-STOCKCODE

HKD O
54.10000 B-PRICE

5,673,001 B-QTY

100,900 B-QTY

10,056,900 B-QTY

00005 B-STOCKCODE
HSBC I-STOCKCODE
HOLDINGS I-STOCKCODE
PLC I-STOCKCODE

00005 B-STOCKCODE
HSBC I-STOCKCODE
HOLDINGS I-STOCKCODE
PLC I-STOCKCODE

Date O
: O
28FEB2022 B-DATE

A O
/C O
name O
: O
NG B-NAME
YEE I-NAME
MEI I-NAME

A O
/C O
no O
: O
773-183280-085 B-ACCNUM

Branch O
HEAD O
OFFICE O
Period O
: O
From O
01FEB2022 B-DATE
to O
28FEB2022 B-DATE

00005 B-STOCK
HSBC I-STOCK
HOLDINGS I-STOCK
PLC I-STOCK
[SHS O
] O

3,001 B-QTY
HKD B-PRICE
54.10000 I-PRICE
162,354.10 O

